Sibusiso Khoza

City of Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa



sbusiso.khoza5@gmail.com



0749139409



linkedin.com/in/sibusisokhozasa

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the Ed-Tech industry. Skilled in Programming, Curriculum Development, Teacher Training, and Web Development. Strong software engineering principles (OOP), Currently enrolled for a Bachelor's degree focused in Applied Mathematics and Computer Science from University of South Africa.

Experience



Head of Teacher Training and Curriculum Development

Code for Change

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)



Coding League Manager

Code for Change

Jun 2018 - Present (4 years 8 months)



CodeJIKA.com

Curriculum Developer

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Education

University of South Africa/Universiteit van Suid-Afrika

Bachelor's degree, Applied Mathematics and Computer Science 2018 - Dec 2023



University of Pretoria/Universiteit van Pretoria

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering

Jan 2013 - 2018



Diepsloot Combined School

National Senior Cetificate, Physical Sciences, Mathematics, Computer Application Technology, Life Sciences, English and IsiZulu 2006 - Dec 2012



Cisco Networking Academy

Licenses & Certifications

- HTML/CSS TestDome
 99dd19223e414100a3dc26ddd3c6e430
- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- **Fundamentals of digital marketing** Google Digital Garage BRW 25N 6VR
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- **Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals** Microsoft
- HTML Essential Training LinkedIn
- in CSS Essential Training LinkedIn
- in JavaScript Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Search Techniques for Web Developers LinkedIn
- in Learning ECMAScript 6+ (ES6+) LinkedIn
- in NoSQL Essential Training LinkedIn
- in Learning REST APIs LinkedIn
- in Git Essential Training: The Basics LinkedIn
- React.js Essential Training (2020) LinkedIn
- in Node.js Essential Training (2019) LinkedIn
- in SQL Essential Training LinkedIn
- in DevOps Foundations LinkedIn

- in Become a Full-Stack Web Developer LinkedIn
- Programming Foundations: Fundamentals LinkedIn
- in Programming Foundations: Databases LinkedIn
- in Learning Python LinkedIn
- in Learning SQL Programming LinkedIn
- in Web Programming Foundations LinkedIn
- Succeeding in Web Development: Full Stack and Front End LinkedIn
- in Learning Java LinkedIn
- in Learning C# LinkedIn
- Programming Foundations: Web Security LinkedIn
- in Become a Software Developer LinkedIn
- in WordPress 5 Essential Training LinkedIn
- m WordPress 5 Essential Training: Site Administration LinkedIn
- in WordPress: Workflows LinkedIn
- in Version Control for Everyone LinkedIn
- in WordPress: Building Child Themes LinkedIn
- Making Sense of the CSS Box Model LinkedIn
- in WordPress: Accessibility LinkedIn

- in WordPress: Custom Post Types and Taxonomies LinkedIn
- in WordPress: Advanced Custom Fields LinkedIn
- in Become a Junior WordPress Developer LinkedIn
- in Learning MySQL Development LinkedIn
- in Become a Database Developer LinkedIn
- in Excel: VLOOKUP and XLOOKUP for Beginners LinkedIn
- in Excel: PivotTables for Beginners LinkedIn
- in Excel: Macros and VBA for Beginners LinkedIn
- in Excel: Filtering Data for Beginners LinkedIn
- in Excel: Conditional Formatting for Beginners LinkedIn
- Excel: Power Pivot for Beginners (2019) LinkedIn
- in Excel: Power Query for Beginners LinkedIn
- in Excel Boot Camp LinkedIn

Skills

Web Development • Microsoft Azure • Curriculum Development • Teacher Training • Discrete Mathematics • Responsive Web Design • Training • HTML5 • HTML • Training & Development